Guide to the Allan Cox Papers SC0343
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Papers
  - Problems (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Kostov, Clement (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Galapagos (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - AAAS Symposium (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - A resubmission of the Proposal to the National Science Foundation (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - June - SF 1977 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Proposal Reviews - Paleomagnetic Investigation of the Tarim Craton, China (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Misc. Graph Paper (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Local Magnetic Anomaly Profiles Shikoku Basin Northwestern Pacific Ocean (Chart) (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Magnetism, the Sphere and Plate Rotation (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Magnetism and the Sample (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Magnetism and the Sphere (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Magnetism, the Sphere and Plate Rotation (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - The Equal-Area Projection and the Continents (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Mail Forwarded to Cox from Stanford to Kenya (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Unfoldered Reprints (Primarily Concerning the Galapagos Geology) (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Several UC Berkeley Publications on the Galapagos International Scientific Project (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Many Issues of Noticiasde Galapagos from July 1963 to 1978 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - The Ohio State University Research Foundation - The Environmental History of the Galapagos Islands (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Prefaces Copy Master (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Chapter 1 - Copy Master (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Chapter 2 - Copy Master (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Chapter 3 - Copy Master (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Thesis References - Copy Master (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Paper 1 Glossies (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Scientific American Illustrations (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Change in Motion of Pacific Plate at 5 MA (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Change in Motion of Pacific Plate at 5 MA (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Motion of Allochthonous Terranes Across the North Pacific Basin Identification of Short Polarity Events by Transforming Marine Magnetic Profiles to the Pole (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Chapter 9 Figures (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Notes (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - San Cristobal - Back Up Notes (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Travel (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - [Unidentified Group Portrait] (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Dating (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Summaries (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - [Unidentified Figure Negatives] (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - XEROX 13 Cox (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Bathymetry - Age (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Denham and Cox (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Cox - 8/24/71 - 9 8x10 Negs. LC (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - [Unidentified Glossie Figures] (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Santa Cruz Maps (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - [Unidentified Glossie Figures] (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Plate Tectonics - Figures and Photos (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Constraints on Terrane Displacement Histories from Plate Kinematics and Paleomagnetism (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - [Unidentified Figures] (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Chapt. 9 Figure Captions (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - [Unidentified Figures] (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - [Unidentified Figures] (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - [Unidentified Figures] (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Ages of the Galapagos Islands (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - [Unidentified Figures] (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - [Unidentified Figures] (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Reversal Freq. Unpublished (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Miscellaneous Awards (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - [Unidentified Figures] (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - [Unidentified Figures] (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - [Unidentified Figures] (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Notes (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Desert Text. New (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Letter from Clement Chase Reviewing an article for publication in Nature (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Cox and Engebretson [Figures] (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Expenses (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - GSA Bulletin Photocopies (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Menard, A Jean Archille (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Paleolat - Back Up (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - References (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Relative Motions Between Oceanic and Continental Plates in the Pacific Basin (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Figures (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Equations (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Allan (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - [Unidentified Figures] (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence Concerning Manuscript - Realtive Motions Between Oceanic and Continental Plates in the Pacific Basin (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Change in Motion of Pacific Plate at 5 MA (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Change in Motion of Pacific Plate at 5 MA (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Relative Motions Between Oceanic Plates of the Pacific Basin (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Paleolatitudes Determined from Paleomagnetic Data from Vertical Cores (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Absolute Plate Motions Predicted from the Age of Subducting Lithosphere (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Donn, W. L. (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Cox Gordon - Chap. 1 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - April 17, 1963 - Constant and Random Vectors Lantern Slides (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - [Unidentified Figures] (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - 3 Illustrations - Angular Dispersions (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Cox, Doell, and Dalrymple - 1963 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - [Unlabeled Figures] (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Binemataths Theory (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - U. of California (1964) Galapagos Symposium Allan Cox (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Illust., Thesis 1 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Cox and Doell - 1962 Illustrations and Slides (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Random Vector (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Photos - Patterned Ground (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - [Unlabeled Figures] (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - [Unlabeled Figures] (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - [Many Reprints] (Box 25, Folder 16)
- Oversized material
  - PRIBILof Spreadsheet (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - PRIBILof Maps (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Scientific American Originals (Photos) (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - A: Misc. Graphs (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - A.N. Khramov (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - To Perfecto (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Polarity Statistics (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - New Zealand Charts (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Misc. Computer Printouts (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Misc. Charts (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Misc. Related Tables (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - MAPWP: Originals, etc. (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - PRIBILof St. Paul (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - VGP's (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - SOHIO (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - MAP: Genovesa (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Poster (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Floreana (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Time Scale Paper (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Time Charts (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Geophysics/Autumn 1982 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - B: Misc. Data (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - 9 Sketches (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Misc. Maps (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Fig. 7 (c+e): Final Design (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - MAPWP Copies (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - F.LOCN (F18): Original & Work (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - New xxx (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Dessert Paper Misc. 6/12/1984 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Rolled Material, Accession ARCH-1986-174
  - Map/chart – Offshore area Southern Coast Ranges San Joaquin Valley 1976 (B. M. Page, Stanford author) (Box 1)
  - Fig. 6A Geologic Column with Gamma Ray-Resistivity Log and Lithographic Section Showing Pennsylvanian and Mississippian Units in the Geary Area (Box 1)
  - Fig. 7A Geary Area. Stratigraphic Section (Box 1)
  - Fig. 7B Geary Area. Stratigraphic Section (Box 1)
  - Unlabelled seismic charts (Box 2)
  - Globe maps with dots, mostly unlabelled (Box 3)
  - Computer plots, Blakely job 1739, 5/25/76 (Box 4)
- Papers, Accession ARCH-1986-194
  - Subject Files
    - Adding R's (Box 1)
    - Analysis of present field from maps (Box 1)
    - Anom. mag red tape (Box 1)
    - Anomaly of SLAB (Box 1)
    - Antarctic project (Box 1)
    - Byerley - calculations (Box 1)
    - Berkeley - engineering geoscience annual report (Box 1)
    - Calculations (Box 1)
    - Calcualtions for e^-t^2/-2 (Box 1)
    - Claerbout course (Box 1)
    - Cocos (Box 1)
    - Cocos - Nature (Box 1)
    - Cosmic Ray Paper (Box 1)
    - Cutler lava - 1st draft (Box 1)
    - Day citation - final (Box 1)
    - Decl., Incl. Data - stat. analysis (Box 1)
    - Dipole variations AGU April, 1960 (Box 1)
    - Dipole variations paper (Box 1)
    - Dipole variation - draft 2 (Box 1)
    - Doell - Scientific American (Box 2)
    - Earth's magnetic field (Box 2)
    - Forum for submitting samples for chemical analysis (Box 2)
    - Galapagos - 1965 (Box 2)
    - Galapagos GISP - 1964 (Box 2)
    - GSA paper (Box 2)
    - Hawaiian "historic" paper - Doell & Cox (Box 2)
    - History of earth's crust (Box 2)
    - Idaho - draft 1 (Box 2)
    - Idaho - inter- & intraflow variations (Box 2)
    - INQUA climatolog (Box 2)
    - INQUA symposium (Box 2)
    - K (Box 3)
    - K - new determination (Box 3)
    - Letters of recommendation 1973-1974 (Box 3)
    - London Q.T. (Box 3)
    - Long period secular variation (Box 3)
    - Manuscripts (Box 3)
    - McKinney-Bancroft SPI*?* paper with Malde & Powers (Box 3)
    - Mohole drafts (Box 3)
    - Mohole manuscript (Box 3)
    - Moho Basalt manuscript (Box 3)
    - Mohole - petrographic descriptions mohole samples (Box 3)
    - MOHO IC520(0-800 ae*?*) (Box 3)
    - MOHO PTRM (Box 3)
    - MOHO manuscript red tape (Box 3)
    - Nairobi University (Box 3)
    - NASA (Box 3)
    - Nature 1960 (Box 3)
    - Nature paper - draft 1 (Box 3)
    - Nature 1963 (Box 3)
    - Nayaguez, P.R. - demog. plots & curves (Box 3)
    - Newcastle 1968 (Box 4)
    - New Zealand Project (Box 4)
    - Nunivak - 1st draft (Box 4)
    - Ohio State (Box 4)
    - Our paper - IAGA 1967 (Box 4)
    - Paleomagnetic study - collection of oriented samples (Box 4)
    - Permissions (Box 4)
    - Peru (Box 4)
    - Peru (Box 4)
    - Pittsburg symposium (Box 4)
    - Polarity intervals (Box 4)
    - Pribilof Islands - page 1 (Box 4)
    - Pucher's results (Box 4)
    - Quaterman Glaciation INQUA NCAR (Box 4)
    - Quat. Journ. (Box 4)
    - Random vector (Box 4)
    - Random vector (cont.) (Box 4)
    - Random vector - calc. (Box 4)
    - Random vector - append. calc. (Box 4)
    - Review - Doell - 1966 (Box 5)
    - Rock glacier notes (Box 5)
    - San Andreas Fault symp. (Box 5)
    - Secular variation (Box 5)
    - Sierra II (Box 5)
    - Snake River reversal - Cox & Malde - outline (Box 5)
    - Sotcher Lake (Box 5)
    - Spinner magnetometer datatron program (Box 5)
    - Spinner Program (Box 5)
    - Stanford talk 1967 (Box 5)
    - Sunset Crater (Box 5)
    - VGP 1945 (Box 5)
    - VGP 1945 - calculations (Box 5)
    - VGP 1945 - illustrations (Box 5)
    - VGP 1945 - material (Box 5)
    - VGP program (Box 5)
    - Vitae (Box 5)
    - Watkins, N.D. - Oregon report (Box 5)
    - Watson & Cox (Box 5)
  - Correspondence
    - 1961 (Box 6)
    - 1962 (Box 6)
    - 1963 (Box 6)
    - 1964 (Box 6)
    - 1965 (Box 6)
    - 1966 (Box 6)
    - 1967 (Box 6)
    - 1968 (Box 7)
    - January-June 1969 (Box 7)
    - July-December 1969 (Box 7)
    - January-June 1970 (Box 7)
    - 1971 (Box 8)
    - 1972 (Box 8)
    - 1972 (Box 8)
    - 1973 (Box 9)
    - 1974 (Box 9)
    - 1975 (Box 9)
    - 1976 (Box 9)
    - 1977 (Box 9)
    - 1978 (Box 10)
    - 1979 (Box 10)
    - 1980 (Box 10)
    - 1981 (Box not specified)
    - Atwater,Tanya - 1 (Box 11)
    - Atwater, Tanya - 2 (Box 11)
    - Atwater, Tanya - 3 (Box 11)
    - Atwater, Tanya - 4 (Box 11)
    - Atwater, Tanya - 5 (Box 11)
    - Anderson, Don L. (Box 11)
    - Austin, S. (Box 11)
    - Baag, Czang-go (Box 11)
    - Banerjee (Box 11)
    - Barton, C.E. (Box 11)
    - Belshe, John C. (Box 11)
    - Berg, Joseph (Box 11)
    - Bhattacharyya, B.K. (Box 11)
    - Bishop (Box 11)
    - Blackett (Box 11)
    - Blakely (Box 11)
    - Blakely (Box 11)
    - Bolt (Box 11)
    - Booker (Box 11)
    - Bonhommet (Box 11)
    - Briden (Box 11)
    - Breiner, Sheldon (Box 11)
    - Brock (Box 11)
    - Bull (Box 12)
    - Butler (Box 12)
    - Carmichael (Box 12)
    - Charlesworth, H.A.K. (Box 12)
    - Christensen (Box 12)
    - Clark, Desmond (Box 12)
    - Cue (Box 12)
    - Conrad (Box 12)
    - Cordani (Box 12)
    - Courtillot (Box 12)
    - Cramer, Chris (Box 12)
    - Creer, K.M. (Box 12)
    - Crough (Box 12)
    - Darragh, R.B. (Box 12)
    - Dawson, Cas (Box 12)
    - De Maria (Box 12)
    - Denham (Box 12)
    - Detrick, R.S. (Box 12)
    - Dickinson, W.R. (Box 12)
    - Doell - 1 (Box 12)
    - Doell - 2 (Box 12)
    - Dunlop (Box 12)
    - Einaudi (Box 12)
    - Fitch (Box 12)
    - Fox, Peter (Box 12)
    - Fraioli (Box 12)
    - Freeman, Cooper, & co. (Box 12)
    - Freund (Box 12)
    - Fuller, Michael (Box 12)
    - Gacii (Box 12)
    - Geller (Box 12)
    - Girdler, R. (Box 12)
    - Gordon, Peter (Box 12)
    - Gordon, R. (Box 12)
    - Grafstein, David (Box 12)
    - Graham, Rhea (Box 12)
    - Graham, S. (Box 12)
    - Greaves (Box 12)
    - Gromme (Box 12)
    - Gromme, C.S. (Box 12)
    - Haggerty (Box 12)
    - Hamilton, Warren (Box 12)
    - Hart (Box 12)
    - Hatherton (Box 12)
    - Hay (Box 12)
    - Hayes (Box 12)
    - Hays, Jim (Box 12)
    - Helsley (Box 12)
    - Herold, Cecile (Box 12)
    - Hillhouse (Box 12)
    - Howell (Box 12)
    - Hsu, Ichi (Box 12)
    - Irving, E. (Box 12)
    - Irving, E. (Box 12)
    - Isaacs (Box 12)
    - Jacobs (Box 12)
    - Jacobsen (Box 12)
    - Johnston (Box 12)
    - Jones, Stan (Box 12)
    - Kanamori (Box 12)
    - Kawai, Naoto (Box 13)
    - Kent, Dennis (Box 13)
    - Khan (Box 13)
    - Kinoshita, H. (Box 13)
    - Kjartansson, E. (Box 13)
    - Kletzer (Box 13)
    - Kobayashi, K. (Box 13)
    - Kodama, Ken (Box 13)
    - Kumagai - Matsuyama (Box 13)
    - Lajoi (Box 13)
    - Larson (Box 13)
    - Larson, Roger (Box 13)
    - Leakey (Box 13)
    - Levy (Box 13)
    - Lieberman, Janet (Box 13)
    - Lindsley (Box 13)
    - Lu, Lee (Box 13)
    - Luyendyk, Bruce (Box 13)
    - Macdonald, Ken (Box 13)
    - MacDonald, William (Box 13)
    - Macgregor, W. (Box 13)
    - Malde, H.E. (Box 14)
    - Malin, Peter (Box 14)
    - Marshall (Box 14)
    - May, Steve (Box 14)
    - McDermott, Mark (Box 14)
    - McDougall (Box 14)
    - McElhinny (Box 14)
    - McIntyre, Donald (Box 14)
    - McWilliams (Box 14)
    - Merrill (Box 14)
    - Miller, Joe (Box 14)
    - Miller, Marti (Box 14)
    - Moe, Marian (Box 14)
    - Molnar (Box 14)
    - Morton, Jan (Box 14)
    - Mavko (Box 14)
    - Nagata, Takeshi (Box 14)
    - Nakamura (Box 14)
    - Ndombi (Box 14)
    - Nutsuma (Nakagawa) (Box 14)
    - Ninkovich (Box 14)
    - Nishimura, S. (Box 14)
    - Opdyke (Box 14)
    - Ozima (Box 14)
    - Patel (Box 14)
    - Phillips (Box 14)
    - Picard, M. Dane (Box 14)
    - Poona (Box 14)
    - Press (Box 14)
    - Pucher (Box 14)
    - Pucher (Box 14)
    - Retelny (Box 14)
    - Riedel, W.R. (Box 14)
    - Rikitake (Box 14)
    - Rikitake (Box 14)
    - Rodgers (Box 14)
    - Rona (Box 14)
    - Runcorn, S.K. (Box 14)
    - Saad, Afif (Box 14)
    - Saito, Takao (Box 15)
    - Scharon, LeRoy (Box 15)
    - Schnapp, M.G. (Box 15)
    - Schouten (Box 15)
    - Shield, John (Box 15)
    - Shive (Box 15)
    - Silver (Box 15)
    - Simpson, Bob (Box 15)
    - Singer (Box 15)
    - Sleep, Norm (Box 15)
    - Smirnov, L. (Box 15)
    - Smith (Box 15)
    - Smith, B. (Box 15)
    - Smith, Peter (Box 15)
    - Staples, John (Box 15)
    - Stauber, Douglas (Box 15)
    - Stauder, William (Box 15)
    - Stearns, Stan (Box 15)
    - Stefanovic, Dr. D. (Box 15)
    - Stein, Seth (Box 15)
    - Stoever, Ed (Box 15)
    - Sugimura (Box 15)
    - Sumner (Box 15)
    - Sykes (Box 15)
    - Tacier (Box 15)
    - Te Punga, M.T. (Box 15)
    - Thompson (Box 15)
    - Thrupp, G.A. (Box 15)
    - Ulmer (Box 15)
    - Van Andel (Box 15)
    - Verhoogen, John (Box 15)
    - Verosub (Box 15)
    - Vetlesen (Box 15)
    - Vincenz, S.A. (Box 15)
    - Vine (Box 15)
    - Wahrhaftig, Clyde (Box 15)
    - Wang, Shi-Chen (Box 15)
    - Watkins (Box 15)
    - Watson (Box 15)
    - Wesson (Box 15)
    - Whitney (Box 15)
    - Wilson, Mark (Box 15)
    - Yama-ai, Mitsuko (Box 15)
    - Yamamura, Eric (Box 15)
    - Yeaman, Michael (Box 15)
    - Zoback, M.L. (Box 15)
- Papers, Accession ARCH-1996-005
  - Definitions and units [geomagnetism] - manuscript (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Geology 2 - lecture notes (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Geophysics 51 - lecture notes (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Geophysics 51 - lecture notes, problem sets, etc., 1973-78 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Geophysics 102 - lectures, problem sets (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Geophysics 102 - readings (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Geophysics 190 - lecture notes, problem sets, etc. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Geophysics 190 - lecture notes, problem sets, etc. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Geophysics 190 - lecture notes, problem sets, exams (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Geophysics 190 - lecture notes, problem sets, exams (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Geophysics 250 - lecture notes, problem sets, exams (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Geophysics 250 - lecture notes, problem sets, exams (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Geophysics 250 - lecture notes, problem sets, exams (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Paleomagnetism Research Seminar, 1972 - lectures (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Paleomagnetism Research Seminar, 1972 - lectures (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Paleomagnetism Research Seminar, 1974 - readings (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Reading notes (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Spherical harmonic analysis in geophysics (xeroxed chapter) (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Arthur Day Lecture 1 (geomagnetism and tectonics), 1975 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Arthur Day Lecture 2 (The Discovery that Compasses Once Pointed South), 1975 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Arthur Day Lecture 3 (convection and sea floor spreading and other aspects of plate tectonics), 1975 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Arthur Day Lecture 4 (Teenage Years of a New Paradigm: Shaping the New View of How the Earth Works), 1975 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Films
  - History of the Pacific Basin, Part I, film reel (16mm) (Box 8)
  - History of the Pacific Basin, Part I, film reel (16mm) (Box 8)
  - Central Salina and Point Arena, film reel (16mm) (Box 8)
  - Plate motions are relative to a specific hot spot, film reel (16mm) (Box 8)
  - History of the Pacific Basin, Part I (Northeast Pacific), film reel (16mm) (Box 8)
  - History of the Pacific Basin, Part II, film reel (16mm) (Box 8)
  - History of the Pacific Basin, Part II, film reel (16mm) (Box 8)
  - History of the Pacific Basin, Part II, film reel (16mm) (Box 8)
  - History of the Pacific Basin, Part II (Cox # 9), film reel (16mm) (Box 8)
  - History of the Pacific Basin, Part II (Cox # 18), film reel (16mm) (Box 8)
  - History of the Pacific Basin, Part II (Cox # 19), film reel (16mm) (Box 8)
  - [Computer graphics], film reel (16mm) (Box 8)
  - [Computer graphics], film reel (16mm) (Box 8)
  - [Computer graphics], film reel (16mm) (Box 8)
  - [Computer graphics], film reel (16mm) (Box 8)
  - [Untitled - no leader], film reel (16mm) (Box 8)
  - Evolution of the Pacific Basin, film reel (16mm) (Box 8)
- Computer tapes
  - Circum-Pacific Tectonics Project CPT-m1, computer tape (Box 8)
  - Circum-Pacific Tectonics Project CPT.sc2, computer tape (Box 8)
  - Untitled (some info on tape label), computer tape (Box 8)
  - Untitled (some info on tape label), computer tape (Box 8)
  - Untitled (some info on tape label), computer tape (Box 8)
- Slides
  - Slides (Box 1-6)
- Additional Papers, Accession ARCH-2017-308
  - Correspondence, 1956-197 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1961-1968 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1970, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 8)